<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Owl Call</string>

    <!-- Menu titles -->
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>

    <!-- ======================================================================================= -->
    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <string name="labelTokenUrl">Access Token URL</string>
    <string name="buttomUpdate">Update</string>

    <!-- ======================================================================================= -->
    <!-- About Text Panel -->
    <string name="about_title">Owl Call</string>
    <string name="about_intro">
        This application makes phone call requests directly to Twilio\'s communication services, which in turn, gets you connected to the destination phone device.
        \n
        \nAt this time, contacts are managed using Google Contacts.
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="about_asis">
        Owl Call is offered \"as is\", without warranty or guarantee.
    </string>
    <string name="about_version">
        \nVersion: 1.0
        \nRelease date: November 18, 2017
        \n
        \nThis application is not a Twilio company application, even though it was developed by a Twilio employee, using the Twilio Voice SDK.
    </string>

    <!-- ======================================================================================= -->
    <string name="about_twiliosetup">
        Twilio Account Setup
    </string>
    <string name="about_twilioaccount">
        To use Owl Call, you are required to have a Twilio account with at least one voice capable phone number.
        \n
        \nGo to http://Twilio.com/console to get and manage your account.
        \n
        \nNote, you either have to talk to an adminitrator, or set up your own access token application.
        \n
        \nYou can use a free Twilio Trial account with Owl Call, however, take note of the restrictions. For example, you can only make calls to phone numbers you have pre-verified. For more information, search for \"How does Twilio\'s Free Trial work?\"
        \n
        \nTo manage your contacts, use Google Contacts on your smartphone, or from a laptop computer. In a future version, I plan to include the ability to mantain contact information: name, phone number and number type (mobile or landline, personal or work).
    </string>

</resources>
